$Wiki	Wiki
$EnableSteam	Enable Steam
$EnableSteamHelp	Use Steam overlay to open the website. If disabled, default browser will open over game.
$Key	Key
$KeyCodeHelp	Key to open the website. Only works on Map and Quests menus. Press in map menu to open online map, or while cursor is over a map marker, or over a quest name for info about it.
$Modifier	Modifier key
$ModifierHelp	Modifier key, must be CTRL, ALT or SHIFT. Cancel or unmap for no modifier.
$UseSteamModal	Use Steam modal web browser
$UseSteamModalHelp	Opens the website on a dedicated Steam browser window without the other overlay options. Steam has a bug and sometimes the tab is not closed properly.
$GamepadBind	Gamepad Button
